

# **Huynh Tan Dung**

Internship

Date of birth: May 01, 1998

Gender: Male

**Phone:** 0964318076

Email: dunghuynh.010598@gmail.com

Address: Lien Chieu, Da Nang

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

I am an energetic, creative and positive attitude person. I have strong technical skills as well as soft skills such as communication, management, presentation, organization. I have experience in working as an intern for a company that develops software in Da Nang. I am good at finding solutions, working in a team, researching and applying new technology as well.

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

2016 - 2020	Duy Tan University Software Engineering
Oct 2019	mgm Company English Schoolarshhip
Jul 2019	Axon Active Company Agile and Scrum

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Nov 2019 - Dec 2019	mgm Company Internship Working as a developer on a real project
Feb 2019 - Jun 2019	Narrow Pacific Company Internship

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Valedictorian of a university 2016 A good result in the National high school exam GPA at University 3.82/4.0

#### **SKILLS**

Language	English
Computer	Word, Excel, Powerpoint
Technical	HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Reactjs, SQL, Nodejs, Java, Git,
Other	Finding solutions, Organization, Numerical, Communication, Leadership

# **HOBBIES AND INTEREST**

Football/Volleyball Chess

Research new technology